questions = [
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "category": "History",
                "question": "The USS Missouri (BB-63) last served in the Korean War.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                "question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "hard",
                "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "medium",
                "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "Geography",
                "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "Geography",
                "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            }
]
